danpena.co.uk 2019-06-06

# The Official Website of Dan Pena. Founder of QLA Methodology | Dan Pena

Danpena.co.uk will only collect basic personal data about you which does not include any special types of information or location-based information.  
This does however include information such as name, email and addresses. This data is used for us to be able to send you email updates and newsletters. 

Why we need your data?

We need to know your basic personal data to provide you with information, updates, marketing emails and announcements. We will not collect any personal data from you that we do not need to provide and oversee this information. 

What we do with your data?

All the personal data we process is processed by our staff in the UK however for the purposes of IT hosting and maintenance this information is located on servers within the United Kingdom. No 3rd parties have access to your personal data unless the law allows them to do so. 

We have a Data Protection regime in place to oversee the effective and secure processing of your personal data. We added SSL certification to ensure data is secure in our network. 

How long we keep your data?

We are required under UK tax law to keep your basic personal data (name, address, contact details) for a minimum of six (6) years after which time it will be deleted permanently. Your information we use for marketing purposes will be kept with us until you notify us that you no longer wish to receive this information. If you want your data to be removed permanently kindly contact us at [webmaster@danpena.co.uk](mailto:webmaster@danpena.co.uk). 

What we would also like to do with your data?

We would however like to use your name and email address to inform you of our future offers and similar products. This information is not shared to any third party not connected to us. You can subscribe at any time via our site to obtain downloaded contents and also get notified about our newsletters and updates. 

What are your rights?

If at any point you believe the information we process on you is incorrect you can request to see this information, and have it corrected or deleted. If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your personal data, you can contact us to have the matter investigated. You can contact us at [webmaster@danpena.co.uk](mailto:webmaster@danpena.co.uk)

If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are processing your personal data not in accordance with the law you can lodge your complaints to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) via their website: <https://ico.org.uk/>. 

Danpena.co.uk will only collect basic personal data about you which does not include any special types of information or location-based information. This does however include information such as name, email and addresses. This data is used for us to be able to send you email updates and newsletters. 

Why we need your data?

We need to know your basic personal data to provide you with information, updates, marketing emails and announcements. We will not collect any personal data from you that we do not need to provide and oversee this information. 

What we do with your data?

All the personal data we process is processed by our staff in the UK however for the purposes of IT hosting and maintenance this information is located on servers within the United Kingdom. No 3rd parties have access to your personal data unless the law allows them to do so. 

We have a Data Protection regime in place to oversee the effective and secure processing of your personal data. We added SSL certification to ensure data is secure in our network. 

How long we keep your data?

We are required under UK tax law to keep your basic personal data (name, address, contact details) for a minimum of six (6) years after which time it will be deleted permanently. Your information we use for marketing purposes will be kept with us until you notify us that you no longer wish to receive this information. If you want your data to be removed permanently kindly contact us at [webmaster@danpena.co.uk](mailto:webmaster@danpena.co.uk). 

What we would also like to do with your data?

We would however like to use your name and email address to inform you of our future offers and similar products. This information is not shared to any third party not connected to us. You can subscribe at any time via our site to obtain downloaded contents and also get notified about our newsletters and updates. 

What are your rights?

If at any point you believe the information we process on you is incorrect you can request to see this information, and have it corrected or deleted. If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your personal data, you can contact us to have the matter investigated. You can contact us at [webmaster@danpena.co.uk](mailto:webmaster@danpena.co.uk)

If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are processing your personal data not in accordance with the law you can lodge your complaints to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) via their website: <https://ico.org.uk/>.
